Guide to the Time Inc. Company Services Records 1969-1983 MS 3009-RG 53
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Company Services Records
1969-1983
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 53
3 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
Time Inc. Company Services was founded in the late 1940s to carry out functions not directly related to the production of Time Inc. magazines or other products. The collection consists of flight logs of an aircraft owned by Time Inc. and invoices for purchase of various items of office furniture and equipment.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Please contact manuscripts@nyhistory.org prior to your research visit to coordinate access. Keep in mind that it will take between two (2) and five (5) business days for collections to arrive, and you should plan your research accordingly.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in two series: Series I. Flight Logs; and Series II. Purchasing Department.
Historical
Time Inc. Company Services was founded in the late 1940s to carry out functions not directly related to the production of Time Inc. magazines or other products. It handled the internal telephone network in Time Inc. buildings, purchasing of furniture and other office equipment, reception of mail, and at some points business travel arrangements for Time Inc. employees.
Citation: Time Inc. Reference Files, MS 3009-RG 3, New-York Historical Society
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Materials
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library. Additional materials about Time Inc. Company Services can be found in the the Time Inc. Subject Files (MS 3009-RG 1) and Time Inc. Reference Files (MS 3009-RG 3).
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of flight logs of an aircraft owned by Time Inc. and invoices for purchase of various items of office furniture and equipment.
Corporation records; Corporations -- History; Corporations -- New York (State) -- New York.; Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Organization files; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- History
- Series I: Flight Logs, 1969-1977; 2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  Scope and Contents
  Series I consists of two identical copies of flight logs for an aircraft owned by Time Inc. The plane was designated #N4764R.
  Arrangement
  Series I is in original order.
  - Flight Logs, 1969-1977 (Offsite-box 4091, Folder 1-9)
  - Flight Logs, 1969-1977 (Offsite-box 4092, Folder 1-9)
- Series II: Purchasing Department, 1980-1983; 1 Linear feet in 1 record carton
  Series II consists of invoices for purchase of various items of office furniture and equipment.
  Series II is arranged alphabetically.
  - Edward Axel Roffman Associates Inc., 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 1)
  - Guardsmark, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 2-4)
  - Intrex and Karman Ltd., 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 5)
  - Kramer, 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 6)
  - Lane - Lanier - Litton Industries, 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 7)
  - Manhattan Office Supplies, 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 8)
  - Meadowlands New Jersey Project: Charles H. Winecoff Associates Inc: Harter Corporation, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 9)
  - R&G Affiliates, 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 10)
  - Rialto Furniture Company, 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 11)
  - Time Inc. Data Center Lyndhurst, New Jersey: Capital Items, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 12)
  - Victor Adding Machine, 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 13)
  - W Complete, 1983 (Offsite-box 4093, Folder 14)